streetdirectory.com 2001-08-15

# Streetdirectory.com

**Virtual Map and its site Streetdirectory.com** pledge to protect their customers’ and users’ privacy online.  This page explains the policy.  The policy may be updated periodically.  You can contact [webmaster@virtual-map.com](mailto:webmaster@virtual-map.com) for more information as necessary. 

### Collection of personal information

**Virtual Map ([www.virtual-map.com](http://www.virtual-map.com/)) and Streetdirectory.com ([www.streetdirectory.com](http://www.streetdirectory.com/)) **do **not** collect any personal information of its sites’ users unless specifically stated.  However, to use certain services of the sites, such as receiving the newsletters or using personalized services or participating in contests, some information may be collected.  The information asked may include your name, email address, birth date, gender, address, postal code, occupation, industry, car ownership and personal interests.  Such information is collected for us to provide you better service and its amount is kept to the minimum and made optional whenever possible.  At least a valid email address is often required by us to serve you better. 

To use our e-commerce services, other additional information such as a credit card number may be necessary to execute the transaction and will be provided to the party handling the transaction.  In the e-commerce sections of our site, we use the industry standard SSL encryption (SSL = secure socket layer).  You are encouraged to review the privacy policies of these third party service providers.

To use other services such as fleet management and vehicle locator services various information of the company may be required.  Unless otherwise stated, this policy applies to all such information as well.  The use of such services will be password protected and uses SSL encryption. 

### Collection of aggregate information

We collect aggregate data of our users (statistics such as “xx% of our users are from overseas”) but it is not possible to extract personal information from this data. 

### Use of cookies

Virtual Map’s sites themselves do not use cookies.  A cookie is a small text file sent to your computer's hard drive. However, our ad serving provider Engage Media uses cookies. 

_**Streetdirectory.com** uses the services of Engage for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing messages. To do this, Engage collects anonymous data through the use of cookies. To learn more about Engage, including your ability to opt out of the Engage system, go to [**_http://www.engage.com/privacy_**](http://www.engage.com/privacy)._ __

### Sharing of information

We do not sell, rent, share or otherwise make available any personal information of users of our sites to other companies or individuals unless specifically stated so or if required by law. 

### Storing of information

To provide better service, we store personal information provided by the users.  It is stored as securely as possible and is only used for its intended purpose. 

We may store users’ correspondence with the company but only if that is considered necessary to provide better service in the future. 

### Security of Internet

We do our utmost to guard your rights and privacy when using our sites.  However, due to nature of Internet, information transmission over it cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure and users give their personal information at their own risk.  Note also that if you make your own private information available for instance in a guestbook, message board or classified ads, that information can be used by others.  We advise you to exercise caution in sharing your personal information over the Internet. 

### Feedback

We welcome any feedback on this privacy policy or other concerns of yours.  Please write to [webmaster@virtual-map.com](mailto:webmaster@virtual-map.com).
